Good morning.
早上好.
Morning. Is there any coffee?
早上好,有咖啡吗?
Mm-hm. I just made it.
Mm-hm.我刚煮好.
Do you want a muffin?
你想要块松饼吗?
No, thanks. I'll get something at work.
不,谢谢. 我会在上班时吃点什么的.
Do you want a cup, Nancy?
你想来杯咖啡吗,Nancy?
Yes, please.
是的,请给我倒一杯.
Is Beth awake?
Beth醒了吗?
More or less. She'll be right down.
差不多了.她马上就下来.
I'm giving her a ride to school.
我要开车送她去学校.
Very clever, Counselor Hobart.
真聪明,Hobart律师.
She will get out of bed for a lift.
为了坐你的车她会起床的.
What is your day like?
你今天有何安排?
I go to the office this morning.
我上午去办公室.
And I'm in court this afternoon.
下午要出庭.
I won't be home late -about 6:30.
今天到家不会太晚  大概6:30.
How about you?
你呢?
Yvonne and I have a meeting with a client.
Yvonne和我约了一个客户见面.
Which client?
哪个客户?
Bill Collins.
We're almost finished with his condo.
他那套公寓的装修设计我们快做完了.
I'll show you pictures tonight.
我今晚会给你看图片.
Do you want a muffin?
你想要松饼吗?
I will make you a muffin.
我给你弄一块.
No, no, no. This is fine.
不不不,这就够了.
Good morning, Beth.
早上好,Beth.
Hi, honey.
你好,宝贝.
I'm very well this morning, thank you.
我今天感觉不错,谢谢.
Would you like a muffin?
想来块松饼吗?
Do you want some yogurt?
要酸奶吗?
-An egg?  -Mom!
-鸡蛋呢?  -妈妈！
Eggs are good.
鸡蛋很不错.
I'm not hungry.
我不饿.
Beth, you really must eat something.
Beth,你真的必须吃写些东西.
How about some cereal?
来点儿麦片怎么样?
Dad, make her stop.
爸爸,叫她别说了.
Breakfast is the most important meal of the day. Bye.
早饭可是一天中最重要的一餐.再见.
-Bye.   -Bye. See you tonight.
-再见.  -再见.晚上见.
-Richard!  -Dad!
-Richard!  -爸爸!
You were taking Beth to school!
你说过要送Beth去学校的.
Oops! Well, then I will have a muffin.
Oops! Well,那我吃块松饼.